{
    "id": "427d14ddc091478aacc51731d79cffca",
    "title": "Little vs. Few",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There was ………………………….. chance of success.",
            "description": "Use little with uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I know ………………………….. man who works in Germany.",
            "description": "Use a before nouns with consonant sounds. ",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "any"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have invited …………………………. of my friends to dinner.",
            "description": "All of these are possible here with different meanings. ",
            "answers": [
                "a few",
                "some",
                "most",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. of my friends are non-smokers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "Whole",
                "Every"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have written to ……………………….. friend I have.",
            "description": "Use every before a singular noun.",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "every",
                "whole"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Hurry up! We haven’t got …………………………. time.",
            "description": "Use much with uncountable nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "little"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Add ………………………….. more salt to the soup.",
            "description": "A little indicates a small quantity. ",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "a little",
                "the little"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… criminals are non-violent.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Every",
                "Most",
                "Each"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He has so ………………………… followers on social media.",
            "description": "Use many before a plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There aren’t …………………………. flowers on the rose.",
            "description": "Use many with plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. child needs love.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Every",
                "All",
                "Whole"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The ………………………… town was under water.",
            "description": "All goes before the article. Whole goes after the article. ",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "most",
                "whole"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}